This L-step has a little bit more athletic approach to it because it involves a squat.
In a squat make sure you get your weight back into your heels and not into the knees just for safety.
It is going to be better on the knee if your hips go back.
So we begin our L-step off to the left side of the bench leading with the right foot.
I start my L, step and put a squat, I'm going to do a little pendulum kick and then exit the bench.
So lift, squat, pendulum kick and down.
Eight counts to each side.
Really add some power to this because it really makes it fun.
Step, lift, squat, little pendulum and down.
Step, jump, squat, pendulum and down.
It comes off of the basic L-step so if you are getting a little winded in class or the intensity level is too high go back to your basic L-step or add the fun put up and squat, pendulum, so we call squat and the pendulum kick and exit the bench for the L squat step.